-=TLF字幕组=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
反恐24小时
第九季 第12集
前情提要
我们给你钱开发装置
We pay you to develop the override
不是让你公之于众的
Not for you to give it away to the rest of the world.
你跟程合作？
You're working with cheng?
你疯了吗？
Are you insane?
克罗伊
奥布赖恩
他绑架了杰克，把他关在
Cheng kidnapped jack, had him put in a secret prison
北京郊外的密牢里，拷问了一整年
Outside of beijing and tortured him for over a year.
奥德莉去找他
When audrey went to go look for him
也被关了起来
he did the same thing to her.
你也没什么利用价值了
I really don't have any use for you anymore.
发吧
Send it.
信息已发送
射击指令，击沉中国沈阳号航母
Fire order. We're to sink the chinese carrier shenyang.
发射一号和二号鱼雷！
Fire torpedoes one and two!
主席先生，我们知道是谁造了
Mr. President, we know who issued
伪令击沉你们航母
The false order that sank your carrier.
程志
Cheng zhi.
程死了
Cheng is dead.
我们有可靠证据表明他还活着
We have reliable evidence that he's alive
眼下在英国
And he's here in England.
我方航母的沉没
Our carrier sinking
和上千船员的死
And the deaths of thousands of crewmen
是赤裸裸的战争行为
is a brazen act of war that cannot go unanswered.
你务必要找到程
It's imperative that you find cheng
还有遥控装置，这样才能向中方解释
and the override device, so that we can show the chinese
击沉航母不是我们所为
that we were not responsible.
鲍尔阴魂不散
Bauer is still in the picture.
你应该除掉他的
You were supposed to have taken him out.
我派了小队找他
I sent a team to recover him.
他不找到我绝不会罢休
He's not gonna stop until he finds me.
程 志
我的人会在码头与你接头
My people will meet you at the dock.
一小时内就能离开英国
You'll be out of the country in less than an hour.
带上她
bring the witness.
她脑袋里的东西很有价值
What's in her head is extremely valuable.
你串通俄国人陷害我，王八蛋
You set me up for the russians, you son of a bitch.
为什么？
Why?
办公厅主任
马克·布德罗
我那时以为鲍尔是个叛徒
I thght bauer was a traitor.
我以为他来这里是要谋杀你
I thought he's here to assassinate you.
俄国人逼我们交出鲍尔
The russians have been pushing us for four years
已经四年了
to turn him over to them.
我在引渡令上伪造了你的签名
I forged your signature on the rendition order.
我要以叛国罪逮捕你
I am placing you under arrest for treason.
总统先生，我还要用到他
Mr. President, I can still use him.
我需要他为我们约见一下
I'm gonna need him to set up a meet.
他在大量失血，拿条毛巾来！
He's bleeding out. Get me a towel now!
程在哪里？
Where is cheng?
我的国家永远不会忘记
My country has not forgotten.
他们也绝不会放弃追杀你
They will not give up until you
直到你血债血还
pay for what you have done.
我和中国驻伦敦使馆有联系
I have a contact at the chinese embassy here in london.
奥德莉·布德罗
我会安排会面
Let me arrange a meeting
带上我能搜集的证据
and I will bring evidence
来说明此次系统入侵
That the penetration of our systems
不是我们所能控制的
was out of our control.
那就请你尽快把这个带给你父亲
Please take this to your father as quickly as possible.
萧，多谢了
Jiao... Thank you.
我手下的枪口正瞄准着你
My associate has his weapon trained on you.
坐回凳子上别动
Sit back down on the bench and don't move.
这样或许我会留你一命
Maybe I'll allow you to live.
以下事件发生在
晚上22:00 至早上11:00 之间
基弗·萨瑟兰
伊冯娜·斯特拉霍夫
泰特
多诺万
翻译 筱宸葭
萧？
Jiao?
玛丽·莱恩
莱杰斯库
翻译 JasonLee
天啊
My god.
翻译 不再的华年
威廉·德韦恩
格本加
阿金纳格贝
翻译 lady5bird
跟你说了，坐在凳子上别动
I told you, you may not move from the bench.
可是我朋友还活着
But my friend is still alive.
我不能坐视不管
Let me go see if I can help her.
基姆·瑞弗
我不会逃跑
I won't run.
校对 LordVader
我向你保证
I give you my word.
我要看看她伤得如何
I'm going to her to see if I can help her.
客 串
马志
斯坦利·汤森
不要出声
Do not scream.
不要和任何人联系
Do not communicate with anyone in any way.
罗斯·麦克科尔
布兰科·托莫维奇
为什么这么做？
Why are you doing this?
米兰达·雷森
亚当·辛克莱
菲利普·温彻斯特
你想干什么？
What do you want?
科里·约翰逊
凯文·麦克纳利
大卫·伊普
再敢离开凳子
You move from the bench again
斯蒂芬·弗雷
我手下会杀了你
My sniper will kill you.
特效 筱宸葭
坐下
Sit.
剪 辑
斯科特·鲍威尔
统筹 筱宸葭
这些好像都是斯托纳维奇的私人邮件
Stolnavich's e-mails all look like they're personal.
艺 术 指 导
乔纳森·李
与家人，不同女人的往来邮件
To family, different women.
会不会是加密过的？
Could it be in some sort of code?
摄 影
杰弗里 C·麦咖特
即便加密过，斯托纳维奇也不会
Stolnavich wouldn't have kept something like
就这么放在明处的
that in the open even if it was coded.
音 乐
肖恩·卡勒里
制作人
金相圭
我找到了三天前用假名
I got e-mails from three days ago using a false name
支付货船货款的邮件
and arranging for payments for a shipment.
今晚离开
Leaves tonight.
程一定会上那艘船
Cheng's got to be that shipment.
40分钟内他会登上港口的某艘货船
He's gonna be on a freighter from the harbor in less than 40 minutes.
好，我叫支援
Okay, I'll call it in.
我让埃里克马上派一队人过去
I'll get erik to send a team there right now.
天啊
Oh, my god.
怎么了？
What is it?
我是摩根特工
This is agent morgan.
马上派一队人去南安普顿
I'm gonna need a team sent down to south hampton.
根据时间来看，是在不到1分钟前拍的
This time stamp...this was taken less than a minute ago.
挂断电话
Hang up the phone.
快挂断电话
Hang up the phone now.
我再打给你
I'll call back.
联合执行制片人
托尼·巴士加仑普
喂？
Yes?
别再追踪我
Stop tracking me.
只要我安全离开后，我会放了她
As soon as I'm safely away, I will set her free.
监 制
布莱恩·格雷泽
基弗·萨瑟兰
要是你追踪我或者有人去救她
If you come near me or anyone try to help her
她会立刻没命
She dies instantly.
程，听我说
Cheng, please listen to me...
这是我的条件！
Those are my terms!
听到了吗？
Is that clear?
听到了
Yes.
程？
Cheng?
这么说，没辙了
So... It's over.
我们不能追踪他
We...We can't go after him.
抓住程是避免与中国
Getting to cheng is the only way
爆发战争的唯一办法
we're gonna stop this war with china.
你真是自以为是
You're just assuming that.
我们无法保证能找到魏主席要的证据
We don't know if we can get the proof to president wei!
即便找到了，他也不一定会退步
or even if he'll back off when he gets it.
监 制
强·卡萨
我们不能白白害死奥德莉
We're condemning audrey to death for nothing.
我们没有其他选择
We don't have another choice.
她爱你
She loves you.
闭嘴！
Shut up!
摩根特工
Agent morgan.
监 制
大卫·弗瑞
我们不能让中情局牵扯进来
We can't involve the CIA.
很容易被程发现
Cheng will see them coming from a mile away.
还有什么办法？
What's the alternative?
监 制
罗伯特·科克伦
他说的对，没有其他办法
He's right, there isn't one.
我要去救奥德莉
I need to go after audrey.
杰克，总统直接命令你去抓捕程
Jack, you're under a direct order from the president to go after cheng
你必须服从命令
you got to follow that.
我可以去救奥德莉
I can go after audrey.
监 制
曼尼·科托
你能搞定吗？
You really think you can handle this?
能
Yes.
好，你秘密联系奥德莉办公室
Okay, I want you to contact audrey's office discreetly.
查出她的去向
Find out where she was going.
无论如何，不能惊动中情局
Whatever you do, do not alert the CIA.
你召集一小队人马
I want you to put together a small team.
干掉那个狙击手
You take out that sniper.
你要随时向我汇报
You keep me posted every step of the way.
我会的
I will.
监 制
伊万·卡茨
霍华德·高登
制 作 人
伊恩·史密斯
编 剧
乔尔·苏尔诺
罗伯特·科克伦
总统阁下
Mr. President
我是代理局长埃里克·瑞特
I'm agent erik ritter, acting head of station.
编 剧
曼尼·科托
伊万·卡茨
您的军事顾问被安排在
Your military advisors are set up
楼上的安全通讯简报厅
in our secure comm and briefing facilities upstairs.
谢谢你，瑞特特工
Well, thank you, agent ritter.
导 演
强·卡萨
奥德莉有消息吗？
Have you heard anything from audrey?
15分钟前我和特勤局的人联系过
I checked in on their secret service detail 15 minutes ago.
她和萧还在谈
She and jiao sim were still talking.
鲍尔呢？
What about bauer?
没有鲍尔的消息，阁下
Negative on bauer, sir.
情况如何，上将？
What's our status, admiral?
中方现在派了八只两栖部队
The chinese now have eight amphibious landing groups
向我们在冲绳的基地前进
steaming toward our bases in okinawa.
第一艘中方航母将在接下来半小时内
The first chinese carrier to reach the 12-mile limit
抵达12英里界线
will be in the next half hour.
冲绳
届时，我方第七舰队已进入作战准备状态
At which point, the seventh fleet has standing orders to engage.
他们同时已命令己方核潜艇
Also, they've ordered their nuclear armed submarines
升至三百英尺发射深度
to ascend to 300 feet firing depth.
阁下，我们需要您批准
Sir, we need your authorization
提高核战备应答
to escalate our own nuclear readiness in response.
将潜艇和发射井提到一级戒备
Put our subs and silos on the highest alert.
看能不能接通魏主席
See if you can get President Wei on the line.
女士，你还好么？
Ma'am, are you okay?
你没事吧，亲爱的？
Are you all right, love?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
能借用下电话么？
Can I use your phone, please?
当然可以
Yes. Yes, of course.
您哪位？
Who is this?
杰克，是我
Jack, it's me.
克罗伊，你在哪？
Chloe, where are you?
我被程抓了，然后跳了车
Cheng had me, I jumped out of his truck.
艾德里安死了
Adrian's dead.
我知道
I know.
你收到了我信息
You got my message.
知道他用装置
You know he used the device
对中国航母发动了袭击？
to launch the attack on the Chinese carrier?
知道，要是我活捉了程
Yes, and if I capture Cheng alive
证明他有参与今天的袭击
and can prove his involvement in today's attack
也许就能让中方放弃开战
we might be able to get China to back down from war.
你知道他在哪么？
Do you know where he is?
他正准备乘货船逃走
He's leaving on a cargo ship.
贝尔切克会在码头与我碰面
Belcheck's meeting me down at the docks.
你不能盲目行动
You can't go in there blind.
我在米尔斯伍德，离码头不远，过来接我
I'm at Millswood, not far from the docks. Come get me.
我帮你调试通信设备
I'll run comm for you.
弄到卫星平面图
I'll get you satellites, schematics.
克罗伊，我想这不行
Chloe, I don't think that's a good idea.
杰克，我知道你信不过我
Jack, I know you don't trust me.
艾德里安骗了我
Adrian lied to me.
我错在不该信他
The only thing I did wrong was to believe him.
拜托，让我将功补过
Please, let me make this right.
你在哪条街，我来接你
Give me your cross streets, I'll pick you up.
魏主席随时可以通话
President Wei, whenever you're ready.
开始吧
Go.
主席阁下
Mr. President.
恕我直言
Forgive me for being blunt.
贵方海军正驶向冲绳
You've got your navy heading toward Okinawa
我方第七舰队也准备戒防
which our seventh fleet is ready to defend.
但避免热战才符合双方利益
But it's in both our interests to avoid a shooting war.
尤其是在我们双方
Especially with both our countries
高度核战备的情况下
at a high level of nuclear readiness.
是你们寻衅
The destruction of our carrier
击沉我方航母，杀死我们士兵
and the deaths of our soldiers is a provocation.
我军必要做出回应
Our military must respond.
我们派出特工
We have agents in the field
正在追捕程志
in the process of apprehending Cheng Zhi.
这是事实
While that's happening
我诚心请求您出于善意
I'm asking you, as a gesture of good faith
停止海军前进
to halt your naval advance.
我们军队官方认定
Our military's official position
程已经死了
is that Cheng is dead.
除非有其他证据
Myself and my allies in the Politburo
我和中共政治局的同党们，只能这样相信
must accept this is true, unless proven otherwise.
您已说得够清楚了，主席阁下
You've made yourself clear, Mr. President.
那我也把话讲明白
Let me make myself clear.
一旦您的军队越过冲绳外围12英里界限…
Once your forces cross the 12-mile limit outside of Okinawa...
我们就开战
We will fight.
让你的人上船，别在这碍眼
Get your men on board and out of sight.
十五分钟后离港
We are scheduled to depart in 15 minutes.
能再快点么？
Is there a way to expedite this?
这会引起不必要的关注
That would draw scrutiny neither of us want.
上船，开始防卫阵地
克罗伊，上车
Chloe, get in.
到底发生什么了？
What the hell happened?
你还好么？
You okay?
嗯，没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
为了摆脱程我被撞了
I got banged up getting away from Cheng.
我们时间不多
We don't have a lot of time.
路上再解释
I'll explain everything while we drive.
你的通信设备呢？
Where is your communications setup?
后座行李箱里
The trunk in the backseat.
克罗伊，你为什么破解遥控装置后
Chloe, I need to know why you were with Adrian Cross
去找了艾德里安·克罗斯
when you took the override device.
杰克，我试图把装置拿回来
Jack, I tried to get the device from Adrian
但他有枪
but he had a gun.
我们随后返回基地，程却在那等着
We got back to the base and Cheng was waiting.
艾德里安不是我想的那种人
Adrian wasn't who I thought he was.
他愚弄了我
He manipulated me
利用我的知识开发了这个装置
and he used my knowledge to create the device.
我也难辞其咎
So, this is partly my fault.
所以我才决定帮你
That's why I need to help you.
我得尽力弥补
I need to try to make this right.
看你吧
It's up to you.
事已至此
At this point
我应该是你唯一的朋友了
I think I'm the only friend you have left.
不论你想不想承认
Whether you want to admit it or not.
任务很简单
The operation's simple.
活捉程
Capture Cheng alive.
为什么自己独干？怎么不请求中情局援助？
Why are you doing this alone? Why not ask the CIA for help?
因为他派狙击手锁定了奥德莉
Because he's got Audrey pinned down by a sniper.
如果他发现任何其他动作就会杀了她
He'll kill her if he sees any operation moving against him.
杰克，对不起
Jack, I'm sorry.
不是你的错，克罗伊
It's not your fault, Chloe.
你要放下这一切
You need to let that go.
这些都别再想了
None of this is.
奥德莉，我是摩根特工
Audrey, this is Kate Morgan.
跟杰克·鲍尔一起共事，我是过来帮你的
I'm working with Jack Bauer. I'm here to help you.
千万不要对我的话作反应
It's really important that you don't react to what I'm saying
不能让狙击手知道
because we don't want the sniper to know
你跟我在联系，明白？
that you're in communication with me. Okay?
明白就点下头
Nod if you understand what I'm saying.
好的，你是否知道狙击手的方位
Okay, I need to know if you have any idea where the sniper is.
不知道就往下看
Look down if the answer is no.
听着，我知道程不想杀你
Listen, I know Cheng doesn't want to kill you.
你得相信这一点
You're gonna have to trust me on this.
我需要你来吸引狙击手的射击
I'm gonna need you to draw the sniper's fire
这样才能精确定位他的位置
so that I can locate exactly where he is.
同意就点下头
Nod if you're still with me on this.
好的，我会数三下
Okay, I'm gonna count to three
数到三你就突然移动
and on three, I need you to make a sudden movement.
准备好了么？
Okay, ready?
一
One
二
Two
三
Three.
定位他了，别动
I've got him. Just stay put
知道我就在附近，好么？
and just know that I'm out here, okay?
她开始逃跑
我开了一枪把她吓回去了
如果情况有变化，就杀了她
杰克
Jack.
你情况如何？
What's your status?
我定位了狙击手
I've located the sniper
但我还得进去
but I need to move into position
这样才能掩护火力让奥德莉逃脱
so I can lay down some cover fire for Audrey to run.
收到，她安全后立即回电
Copy that. Get back to me as soon as you've got her secured.
了解
Got it.
进去四个
Four of us moving in
只会吸引太多注意
is just gonna attract too much attention.
我打头阵
I'm gonna run point.
一旦确认没事
The minute I have a clean line of sight
就按我指令行事
we move on my command.
东西都拿到手了么？
Did you get everything?
拿到了，这里有太多地方给程的人藏身
Yes. There are too many places for Cheng's men to hide.
所以我才在这
That's what I'm here for.
我应该能后门侵入卫星
I should be able to backdoor a satellite
定位他们位置
and get their positions.
蜂窝式调制解调器没有信号，我需要联网
Cellular modem's not giving me a signal. I need to get online.
我能接入那个接收机
I can wire into that dish.
不过还得改编应答器
I need to reprogram the transponders.
我通信畅通，等会再回来
My comm is open. I'll get back to you.
掩护我
Cover me.
克罗伊，等等
Chloe. Wait.
谢谢你做的一切
Thank you for everything.
好运，走
And good luck. Go.
奥德莉，我要进去了
Audrey, I'm about to move into position
这样才能一击必中
where I can get a clean shot on the sniper.
一旦交火
As soon as that happens
听到枪响
the second that you hear gunfire
就往你左肩后的树跑
I want you to run toward the tree behind your left shoulder.
做好准备
Okay, stand by.
杰克，我从后门侵入了一颗上方卫星
Jack, I'm backdoored into a satellite overhead.
切换红外中
Resolving the infrared.
好，能看到你和贝尔切克了
Okay, I can see you and Belcheck.
现在安全，行动
You're clear. Go.
停住，杰克，两个守卫正朝你们过来
Stop, Jack. You have two guards coming straight at you.
准备好了吗？
Ready?
动手
Now.
杰克，集装箱上还有一个
Jack, there's another guy on top of the container.
五点钟方向
Five o'clock.
收到
Got it.
从这边抄过去，走
Turn here. Go.
杰克，你得干掉两个守卫
Jack, you'll have to take out
他们在码头那边
two guards on the port side.
船桥上有些人
There are men on the bridge.
他们正离开
They're moving away.
好了，安全了，快走
You're good. Clear. Go.
收到
Copy that.
同时开火
Synchronized shot.
我负责左边那个，你瞄准右边那个
I've acquired target on the left, you take target on the right.
听我指令，三，二，一，开火
On my count. Three, two, one, fire.
克罗伊，我们上船了
Chloe, we're on the boat.
杰克，你左边梯子顶上有一个人
Jack, you have a man at the top of the stairs to your left
你正前方集装箱上还有一个
there's another one on the container directly in front of you.
通过热能图像显示，我还捕捉到了12人
I'm picking up about a dozen other heat signatures on the ship
大多两人一组
mostly in pairs.
收到
Copy that.
奥德莉那边什么情况？
What's the status on Audrey?
还没收到任何消息
I haven't heard anything.
大部分守卫都在指挥塔
Most of the men are in a defensive formation
四周戒备，程一定在那里
around the comm tower-- that must be where Cheng is.
带我们进去
Guide us in.
好
Okay.
长官，扫描显示附近有人
Sir. I've been running scans-- someone in the immediate area
黑进了本地卫星
is downstreaming with a local satellite.
呼叫你所有手下
Roll-call your men.
马拉，报告
帕维尔，听到没有？
不管是谁黑进了卫星
Whoever's linking to the satellite
你能切断通讯路径和联络吗？
can you cut the access and the communication?
可以，我能把信号回传到我的屏幕上
Yes, and I can redirect their feed to my screen.
赶快做
Do it.
呼叫剩下的全部人手，叫他们把人找出来，快去！
Contact whoever's left. Tell them to go find him. Go!
你们跟他去
快点！
他们在搞什么？不
What are they doing? No.
天啊，程志发现我们了
Oh, my God. Cheng knows we're here.
杰克，我得告诉凯特，她必须马上行动
Jack, I have to tell Kate. She needs to move now.
收到
Copy that.
凯特，我是克罗伊
Kate, it's Chloe.
他们在找我们，你必须帮奥德莉脱离险境
They're onto us. You have to get Audrey out of there
快叫中情局的人协助
and get the CIA involved.
我随时就位，克罗伊
I'm about to move into position, Chloe.
程快要命令狙击手开枪了！
Cheng's gonna order the sniper to shoot!
马上把奥德莉弄走，快行动啊
Get Audrey out of there now. Move.
杀了她！
开火！开火！
Engage! Engage!
快！快！快！
Go! Go! Go!
好了，干掉他了
Okay, got him.
上去看看，确保他死了
Get up there and make sure he's dead.
遵命，长官
Yes, ma'am.
奥德莉，你没事吧？
Audrey, are you okay?
没事
Yes.
好的
Okay.
埃里克，我是凯特
Erik, it's Kate.
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我在莫尔登公园，和奥德莉·布德罗一起
I'm at Malden Park with Audrey Boudreau.
通知特勤局，我们已经安全营救了她
Inform Secret Service that we have secured her
正护送她回中情局
and we're taking her back to the CIA.
她的安保呢？
Where's her current detail?
我晚点再跟你解释
I'll explain everything later.
你现在赶快派一个小组赶到南汉普顿码头
Right now you need to get a team over to South Hampton docks.
杰克已经潜入行动了，但是他现在有麻烦
Jack was going in stealth, but right now he's in trouble
他绝对需要你帮助
and he really needs your help
他在全力阻止这场战争
he's trying to stop this war.
凯特
Kate.
战术小组马上全副武装，直升机上待命
I need TAC teams suited up in choppers, now!
杰克，奥德莉安全了
Jack, Audrey's safe.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
他们察觉了我的信号，卫星信号中断了
They found my feed. I lost satellite.
我正全力恢复…
I'm trying to get it back.
克罗伊？克罗伊？
Chloe? Chloe?
杰克？杰克！杰克，收到没有？
Jack? Jack! Jack, do you copy?
连接中断
我已经切断了通讯，接管了他们的卫星信号
I've cut communications and taken over their satellite feed.
这里，这两个…图像…
Here, these two... signatures...
肯定是鲍尔和他的帮手
must be Bauer and whoever he has with him.
我们现在马上出发
We're leaving now.
跟我来
开动引擎
他们准备离港了
They're getting ready to push off.
我需要你下到发动机舱
I need you to get down to the engine room
不择手段阻止开船
do whatever you can to stop
我想办法到桥上去，快！
and I'll make my way to the bridge. Go.
杰克找到程了吗？
Is Jack closing in on Cheng?
是的，程利用你引出了杰克
Yes. Cheng was using you to get to Jack.
所以杰克派我来这里
That's why Jack sent me here.
杰克还好吗？
Is Jack all right?
我不清楚
I don't know.
奥德莉，趴下！
Audrey, get down!
有两人倒地
Got two men down.
天啊，奥德莉
Oh, God. Audrey.
不
No.
打电话给埃里克，告诉他还有一个枪手
Call Erik, tell him we have a second shooter.
把那给我
Give me that.
叫医生过来，赶快！
Get medical here right now!
天啊
Oh, my God.
坚持住
Stay with us.
埃里克，我们需要医生
Erik, we need medical now.
奥德莉，支援马上到
Audrey, help is on the way.
保持清醒，挺住，好吗？
Don't leave me now, okay?
坚持住
Stay with me.
程安排了后备枪手
Cheng had a second shooter.
坚持住，奥德莉，拜托啊
Stay with me, Audrey. Come on.
坚持住
Stay with me.
哦，天啊
Oh, God.
好的，坚持住，坚持住
Okay. Stay with me. Stay with me.
坚持住
Stay with me.
奥德莉，你能坚持…？
Audrey, will you stay with...?
求你了，奥德莉
Please, Audrey.
别，奥德莉
No, Audrey.
求你坚持住，坚持住，拜托了，坚持住！
Please stay with me. Stay with me, okay? Stay with me!
我的天啊
Oh, God.
上将？
Admiral?
空中侦察已确认
Air reconnaissance confirms.
中方两栖舰仍在向我方冲绳基地逼近
The Chinese amphibious groups are still on course for our base in Okinawa.
总统阁下
Mr. President
如果对方冲破了警戒线，我请求采取行动
I need a go-ahead to engage if the perimeter is breached.
杰克那边有消息吗？
Anything from Jack?
恐怕还没有，总统阁下
I'm afraid not, Mr. President.
阁下，我们的部队正等您一声令下
Sir, our forces are awaiting your orders.
知道了，上校
I know that, Colonel.
先生…请借一步说话
Sir... I need a word. Private.
贝尔切克？
Belcheck?
下去把船停住
I got to fall back to reset.
收到
Copy that.
克罗伊
Chloe.
杰克，我是凯特
Jack, it's Kate.
恩，说吧
Yeah, go ahead.
杰克，真对不起
Jack, I'm so sorry.
奥德莉死了
We lost Audrey.
你说什么？你刚才说她安全了
What are you talking about? You said she was safe.
真对不起，实在对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
还有个枪手，他杀了她，杰克
There was another shooter, and he got her, Jack.
我…我真的很对不起
I'm...I'm so sorry.
杰克？
Jack?
杰克，听得到吗？
Jack, can you hear me?
杰克，说话呀
Jack, talk to me.
引擎…把它关掉
Engine...shut them down.
好吧
Okay.
你本该像耗子一样东躲西藏，苟延残喘
You should have stayed hidden like a rat.
你偏要不得好死
You could have died an old man.
警告
进入警戒线12英里
中方已经突破警戒线了，总统先生
The Chinese have breached the perimeter, Mr. President.
警告
进入警戒线12英里
允许交战
Permission to engage.
武器准备随时开火
Set weapon postures red and tight.
你们可以同任何已确认的中国空军
You are cleared to engage any positively-identified
或者水面目标交火
Chinese air or surface targets.
总统先生，事态升级
Mr. President, if this should escalate
我们得开始重审一下核武器应对的方案
we need to begin reviewing the nuclear response scenario.
开始重审
Begin the review.
先生，正在为您接入楼下的紧急来电
Sir, I'm putting through an urgent call from downstairs.
先生们，打扰一下
Excuse me, gentlemen.
现场通讯器上杰克·鲍尔有消息了
I have Jack Bauer on live comm link.
先别下命令
Hold that order.
推迟作战准备
Delay weapon posture red.
接到显示屏上
Putting it up on the monitors.
我是杰克·鲍尔，我抓到程志了，他还活着
This is Jack Bauer. I have Cheng Zhi, and he is alive.
重复，我抓到程了，他还活着
I repeat . I have Cheng, and he is alive.
启动面部识别程序
Initiate facial recognition.
收到，刚刚联系上中方
Copy that. Just connected with the Chinese.
很快就好
Just give me one second.
在录音了
You're being recorded.
告诉他们你是谁
Tell them who you are.
确认了吗？
Do we have confirmation?
马上就好，先生
Just a few more seconds, sir.
面部识别，50%，进行中
声音匹配，20%，进行中
告诉他们你是谁！
Tell them who you are!
我就是程志！
My name is Cheng Zhi!
识别出了吗？
Did you get that?
面部识别，96%，进行中
声音匹配，94%，进行中
你识别出了吗？
Did you get that?
面部识别，100%，进行中
声音匹配，100%，进行中
有了
Got it.
现在既有面部识别又有声音匹配了
That's facial recognition and voice match.
就是他
It's him.
收到
Copy that.
完毕
Out.
给我接通魏主席
Let's get President Wei on the line.
这是为了奥德莉，你个王八蛋
This is for Audrey, you son of a bitch.
主席先生，刚才我们发给您的文件，请问您是否收到？
Mr. President, did you receive the file we just sent you?
我正在观看这份文件
I'm looking at it now.
那您就能看到程还活着，且已被我羁押
Then you can see that Cheng is alive and in our custody.
这证实了我对于沈阳舰沉没
This confirms everything I've told you
所作出的一切解释
about the sinking of the Shenyang.
那并非我的命令
It was not my order.
我们需要核实这份录像
We will need to verify this recording.
您尽可以进行核实，但是同时
Well, you can verify it all you want, but in the meantime
您需要命令您的战舰掉头
you need to turn your ships around.
您的战舰已经越过了我方的防卫界线
Your ships have crossed our defensive perimeter.
如您再不令其掉头
If you don't turn them around
我将被迫做出回应
I'm going to be forced to respond.
可以
All right.
我会令我方战舰撤退
I will instruct our ships to withdraw
但我需要您保证，我们将会商榷对于我方
but I need your assurance that we will discuss reparations
沉没航母及阵亡士兵的补偿问题
for the loss of our carrier and the soldiers aboard.
我保证
You have that.
谢谢您，主席先生
And thank you, Mr. President.
先生，我…
Sir, I, uh...
我们回去之前
Before we head back out
我…需要跟您谈谈
I...need to talk to you.
说吧
Speak.
这事儿有些敏感，先生
It's rather sensitive, sir.
或许…或许您先坐下来
Maybe, uh... maybe you want to sit back down.
我不需要坐下
I don't need to sit down.
发生什么了？跟我说吧
What happened? Tell me.
先生，呃…
Sir, um...
奥德莉出事了
It's Audrey.
她去世了
She's dead.
她在和萧倩碰面的时候被一个狙击手打中
She was shot by a sniper during her meeting with Jiao Sim.
是程的人干的
It was one of Cheng's men.
这肯定是误传
That's got to be a mistake.
她去的是个秘密会面
She was at a covert meeting.
她身边还有特勤局一个分遣队在护卫着
She had Secret Service detail with her.
这不可能！
That's impossible!
那个分遣队的成员，也都被杀光了
Every man on that detail was killed, as well.
真的很抱歉，但这不是误传
I'm so sorry. It's not a mistake.
我们已经收到现场的确认消息
We got confirmation from the field
您的女儿于十分钟前
that your daughter died ten minutes ago
死于枪击
from a gunshot wound.
先生
Sir.
快叫个医生过来，行吗？
Get a medic in here, will you?
二层会议厅需要一个医生
We need a medic at the second floor conference room.
您还好吗？
You okay?
先生，您没事儿吧？轻点，轻点，轻点，轻点
Sir, you okay? Okay. Go easy, go easy, go easy, go easy.
轻点
Easy.
好了
It's okay.
克罗伊？
Chloe?
我们控制住船之后就没有她信儿了
I haven't heard from her since we charged the boat.
克罗伊？
Chloe?
杰克
Jack.
哦，不要，不要
Oh, no. No.
克罗伊！
Chloe!
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
你是谁？
Who is this?
时间？
When?
地点？
Where?
明白
Understood.
我会到的，你安排吧
I'll be there. Just set it up.
12小时后
埃里克
Erik.
这是我的行动后报告
It's my after-action report.
说真的…
Look...
奥德莉的事
What happened to Audrey
并不是你的错
it wasn't your fault.
外勤工作变数太多
Field work is not an exact science.
你不可能预料到
There's no way you could have known
程还会有第二个杀手
that Cheng had a second shooter.
嗯，我…这我明白
Yeah, I, uh... I realize that.
遵总统命令
Per the president's orders
他们会护送你去莱肯希思
these men are going to escort you to Lakenheath
在那里会有架军用运输机送你回国
where a military transport will take you back to the States.
总统怎么样了？
How is the president?
我们说话这会儿，总统正在登上空军一号
The president is boarding Air Force One as we speak.
詹姆斯，我深表遗憾
James, you have my deepest sympathy.
我真是无法想象你现在的痛苦
I can't even imagine what you're going through.
谢谢你，阿拉斯泰尔
Thank you, Alastair.
你一直都是一个很好的朋友
You've been a good friend.
如果有任何我能做的事情，任何事…
If there's anything I can do, anything at all...
没有，你无能为力
No, there's nothing you can do.
任何人都无能为力
Nothing anyone can do.
我们启程来伦敦的前一天
The day before we left for London,
我坐在我的办公室里
I was sitting in my office
看着我桌子上一张美丽的女人的照片
looking at a picture on my desk of a beautiful woman.
我就那么一直看着
I kept staring at it.
从我当政那天起
It's been on my desk
它就在我桌子上摆着
since my first day in office.
我知道我认识那个女人
And I knew that I knew that woman.
可我就是想不起来她的名字
But I couldn't think of her name.
10秒钟，15秒钟，然后，忽地一下
Ten seconds, 15 seconds go by, then, poof.
蓦然记起
Pops into my head.
那是奥德莉啊
It was Audrey.
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我会记不起今天发生的任何事
I won't remember anything that happens today.
我会记不起以往所有事，罢了
I won't remember anything that happens, period.
我会记不起我曾有个女儿，如是惨死
I won't remember that I had a daughter that died in such a horrible fashion.
伦敦郊外
你确定要这么做吗？
Are you sure you want to do this?
是
Yeah.
她先走！
She walks first!
杰克，你不用这么做的
Jack, you don't have to do this.
你该回家了
It's time for you to go home.
你之前说的是对的
You were right about what you said earlier.
你是我最好的朋友
About being my best friend.
谢谢你
Thank you.
有时间就去看看我的家人
Look in on my family when you can.
走吧
Go.
走
我相信你言出必行
I've taken you at your word.
但若你胆敢食言
But if you're lying to me
如果她或者我的家人出了任何事
if anything happens to her or my family
我会让你整个世界分崩离析
your entire world will come apart
而你防不胜防
and you will never see it coming.
我想要的只是你，鲍尔先生
We just want you, Mr. Bauer.
仅此而已
That's all we ever wanted.
我想说你会喜欢莫斯科的
I would say you're going to enjoy Moscow
但你也知道那是假话
but you'd know I was lying.
到车里去
Go to the car.
去
Go.
本季终
更多原创翻译字幕请访问
TLF论坛：http://bbs.eastgame.org
TLF中文字幕站：http://sub.eastgame.org
TLF字幕组微博：http://weibo.com/tlfsubs